

## Minh Duc, Ta

334c Auco Tay Ho District, Hanoi

Mobile +84 904 889 960

Email ductm310@gmail.com

Portfolio dxta.github.io

Profile

I'm 22 years young developer, having over 1 years' experience in back-end web development and cloud services development. I keep atop of new developments within the industry and can adapt quickly to new coding conventions. I'm comfortable working either independently or as part of a team. I'm a creative and enthusiastic developer and I love what I do.

Experience

Developer/Internship, Framgia – July 2012 - August 2013 Web development using Ruby on Rails, MySQL, Ajax Front-end development with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript Mobile application development with Cocos2d-x

Researcher/Internship, High Performance Computing Center of HUST – 2013 - present

Researches into High Performance Computing using GPU Researches into Cloud Computing - bkcloud.org

Education

Hanoi University of Science and Technology, Vietnam – Undergraduate, 2009-present

Technical Skills

	Years' Experience	Skill Level
Languages		
C/C++	3	Intermediate
Python	1	Intermediate
PHP	1	Intermediate
Ruby	2	Expert
Java	1	Novice
HTML/XML	2	Intermediate
CSS	2	Intermediate
JavaScript/jQuery	2	Intermediate
Unix Shell	2	Intermediate
Assembler	1	Novice
UML	2	Intermediate

Framework		
PHP/CakePHP	1	Novice
Ruby/Rails	2	Intermediate
Database		
PostgreSQL	1	Novice
MySQL/MySQL Cluster	2	Intermediate
SQLite	1	Novice
Operating System		
Windows	5	Novice
Linux (Centos, Ubuntu)	5	Expert
Mac OSX	3	Intermediate
Technologies		
CloudStack	1	Intermediate
Cas-Server	1	Intermediate
Zabbix Monitoring Tools	1	Intermediate

References

Dr. Huu Duc, Nguyen

Lecturer/Director of High Performance Computing Center, HUST Email: ducnh@soict.hust.edu.vn

Mr. Xuan Dung, Vu

Director of System Development, Framgia Vietnam Inc.

Email: vu.xuan.dung@framgia.com